Contact

9465 Wilshire Blvd, Suite 700, Beverly Hills CA 90212 310-205-7756 (Work) olga.kapitskaya@rbc.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ olgakapitskaya (LinkedIn) us.rbcwealthmanagement.com (Other) us.rbcwealthmanagement.com/

us.rbcwealthmanagement.com/olga.kapitskaya (Company)

Languages

Russian (Native or Bilingual)

Olga Kapitskaya, CRPC®

Associate Vice President – Financial Advisor at RBC Wealth Management

Beverly Hills, California, United States

Summary

I have been working in the financial industry since 1995 and joined RBC Wealth Management in April of 2022 following more than a decade of professional experience as a financial advisor at Merrill Lynch Bank of America. My professional background includes wealth advisory, institutional equity research, and private equity roles at other leading wealth management firms in New York City and Los Angeles.

One of the reasons I chose a career in the financial services industry, is my desire to help others. This passion stems from witnessing the challenges faced by people in my life and I recognized the need for a caring professional to help others define their goals, establish a wealth management strategy centered on their priorities, and help them adjust their strategy as needed when the inevitable changes in life happen. As a financial advisor I focus on working with women who run private businesses, medical doctors, company executives, and retirees.

Outside of the office, I enjoy traveling with my family, reading about medieval history, and cooking, because it's part science and part magic.

Please visit http://www.rbcwealthmanagement.com/us/en/legal for important disclosure information. Investment and insurance products offered through RBC Wealth Management are not insured by the FDIC or any other federal government agency, are not deposits or other obligations of, or guaranteed by, a bank or any bank affiliate, and are subject to investment risks, including possible loss of the principal amount invested. RBC Wealth Management, a division of RBC Capital Markets, LLC, Member NYSE/FINRA/SIPC.

Experience

RBC Wealth Management Financial Advisor

April 2022 - Present (2 years 10 months)

Los Angeles, California, United States

Merrill Lynch Wealth Management Financial Advisor September 2011 - April 2022 (10 years 8 months)

Pepperdine University
Adjunct Faculty
March 2010 - September 2020 (10 years 7 months)

Morgan Stanley Smith Barney Financial Advisor August 2010 - August 2011 (1 year 1 month)

BetaOne Consulting
Principle
September 2001 - August 2010 (9 years)

Alfred Mann Foundation Analyst October 2008 - January 2009 (4 months)

Stifel, Nicolaus & Co Equity Research Analyst April 1998 - October 2008 (10 years 7 months)

Rodman & Renshaw, Inc. Equity Research Analyst April 1996 - March 1998 (2 years)

Education

Pepperdine University

Master's Degree, Business/Finance · (2003 - 2006)

Long Island University
Bachelor's Degree (1992 - 1994)